http://www.gonzaga.edu/online-policies/gonzaga-university-privacy-statement

Skip Navigation
ZagOn: COVID-19 Resources
Dashboard and testing info, ZagCheck self-screening app, FAQs, visitor guidelines and more.
Social Media User Expectations
Gonzaga University collects a variety of information through this web site. Gonzaga University is the sole owner of all information collected through this site, and it does not sell, share, rent, or otherwise disclose this information except as described in this statement. Information may be collected at various points on the site and may change without notice. Use of this website is voluntary. By using this website, you agree to allow Gonzaga University to collect and use any information you provide through the use of the site, including personally identifiable information (“PII”) and non-personal information as described in this Privacy Statement.
Collection and Use of Non-personal information: Such information cannot be used to identify an individual personally. It is used to monitor site usage, health, and effectiveness, and it is also used to make improvements to the functionality and organization of the site. Non-personal information that may be collected and used includes, but is not limited to:
The Internet Protocol (IP) address and name of the Internet domain used to access the Internet
The IP address of the website that referred the user to the Gonzaga web site
The date and time of access
The pages visited
The web browser and operating system used to access the web site
Search terms used on the site
Collection of Personal information: Users may choose to voluntarily provide information on the site that could be used to identify them personally. This information is strictly voluntary – no personal information is collected unless the user provides it. Personal information that may be collected includes, but is not limited to:
Contact information
Employment information and history
Education history
References
Gift information
University affiliation
Information provided through online forms for a variety of purposes
Use of Personal Information: Gonzaga University may use personal information like that described above for the following purposes (this list may change without notice):
Administer users’ participation in this web site
Communicate information that may be of interest to users
Fulfill requests for services or materials
Contact users
Confirm information provided by users
Process gifts
Conduct research or surveys
Respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process
Facilitate interactions with third parties
Sharing Personal Information: Personal information provided to Gonzaga University through this web site may be available to employees of the University or to authorized third parties who provide services to the University or to the users of this web site (www.gonzaga.edu). Select third parties may be provided with personal information from this web site in order to help the University fulfill its mission. Gonzaga University will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third parties are obligated to protect personal information on its behalf.
Cookies: Gonzaga University uses cookies (small text files installed or updated when a web site is visited) for analysis and to maintain appropriate authentication and authorization boundaries. Users may disable cookies through their browser, but the web site may not function properly when cookies are disabled.
Links to Other Sites: Gonzaga University may provide links to other, third-party web sites from this site. Any such sites are regulated by the privacy policies of the providers of those web sites and not by this privacy statement. Gonzaga University is not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of any third-party sites.
Security: Gonzaga University takes reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy and security of personal information provided by users of this web site. Gonzaga cannot guarantee the security or privacy of information provided to it through this web site. Users provide all such information at their own risk.
